<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<windteam>
	<windsurfers>
		<name>Robby Naish</name>
		<products>Naish Sails, Kites, Stand-up paddleboards</products>
		<claimtofame>Robert Staunton Naish is one of the first athletes to have gained long-lasting international fame in the sport of windsurfing.</claimtofame>
	</windsurfers>
	<windsurfers>
		<name>Laird Hamilton</name>
		<products>Golfboard, Laird Apparel, XPT, Laird Superfood</products>
		<claimtofame>World renowned waterman Laird Hamilton is known as the guiding genius of crossover board sports, and is largely considered the primary influence behind many surfing innovations, including tow-in surfing, stand-up paddle boarding, and hydrofoil boarding. Surfer Magazine has labeled Laird as the sport’s most complete surfer,displaying almost unnerving expertise in a multitude of disciplines, and flat out surfing’s biggest, boldest, bravest, and the best big wave surfer in the world today, bar none.</claimtofame>
	</windsurfers>
	<windsurfers>
		<name>Bjorn Dunkerbeck</name>
		<products>Starboard, Severne, Juice Plus, Ocean/Earth, Slam Park, Dunkerbeck-Eyewear</products>
		<claimtofame>Björn Dunkerbeck (born 16 July 1969) is a professional windsurfer who has won Professional Windsurfers Association (PWA) Overall World Championships a record forty one times.</claimtofame>
	</windsurfers>
	<windsurfers>
		<name>Jason Polakow</name>
		<products>JP-Australia, Neil Pryde, Oxbow</products>
		<claimtofame>Jason Polakow was born in Torquay, Australia, and is a true all-rounder when it comes to extreme sports. Before he switched to windsurfing and made his name as a legend on the water, Jason had already earned the title of Australian Junior Moto X Champion. But at just 18 years old, he established himself as the top windsurfer in Australia and headed off to the world stage, where he quickly rose to the top.</claimtofame>
	</windsurfers>
	<windsurfers>
		<name>Levi Siver</name>
		<products>Red Bull,Quatro, Dakine, Goya, MFC</products>
		<claimtofame>King of Style Levi Siver didn’t take to windsurfing right away – he was born in landlocked Idaho, after all – but once he found his calling, there was no stopping him from reaching the sport’s highest levels. He’s a contest veteran with many wins to his name, but his true passion lies in freestyle windsurfing, where he’s considered a pioneer who’s made his own mark on the sport.</claimtofame>
	</windsurfers>
</windteam>